Contact

809 82nd Parkway Myrtle beach sc 843-692-1410 (Work)

www.linkedin.com/in/dr-jamie-kabanuk-dnp-msn-rn-nea-bc-43903755 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care
Emergency Nursing
Trauma Nursing

Certifications

PALS Provider (Pediatric Advance Life Support)

ENPC

Nurse Executive Advanced (NEA-BC)

ACLS Provider (Advance Critical Life Support)

TNCC

Dr. Jamie Kabanuk DNP, MSN, RN, NEA-BC

Chief Nursing Officer at HCA Healthcare

Charleston, South Carolina

Summary

Transformational leader with several years of nursing experience in acute care, emergency nursing and intensive care specialities of healthcare delivery and management. I am passionate about patient experience, clinical excellence and employee satisfaction. My strengths include managing successful process improvement projects, establishing a shared governance model and leading teams to meet their set goals.

Experience

HCA Healthcare

7 years 1 month

Chief Nursing Officer August 2019 - Present (1 year)

Executive Development Program- CNO Track October 2018 - August 2019 (11 months)

Nashville, Tennessee

Assistant Chief Nursing Officer August 2017 - August 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Myrtle Beach, South Carolina

Director Of Critical Care Services May 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 4 months)

Myrtle Beach, South Carolina Area

Administrative Supervisor/ ED Manager July 2013 - May 2015 (1 year 11 months)

Myrtle Beach, South Carolina

Administrative Supervisor at a busy trauma center. Responsibilities include supervision of staff and management of daily operations.

Served facility as a supervisor in 40 bed ED.

Education

Jacksonville University

Master of Science in Nursing (MSN), Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Chamberlain University

Doctor of Nursing Practice (DNP), Nursing Administration · (2016 - 2018)

Utica College

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2013)